[
  {
    "question": "How many episodes of the TV show 'Friends' were made?",
    "answer": 236
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the height of the Eiffel Tower in meters?",
    "answer": 330
  },
  {
    "question": "How many bones are in the adult human body?",
    "answer": 206
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the top speed, in mph, of a cheetah?",
    "answer": 75
  },
  {
    "question": "How many countries are members of the United Nations (as of 2023)?",
    "answer": 193
  },
  {
    "question": "How many minutes does light take to travel from the Sun to Earth?",
    "answer": 8
  },
    {
    "question": "How many official James Bond films have been released (as of 2025)?",
    "answer": 27
  },
    {
    "question": "How many miles is the Earthâ€™s equator in length?",
    "answer": 24901
  },
    {
    "question": "How many elements are there on the periodic table (as of 2025)?",
    "answer": 118
  },
    {
    "question": "How many paintings did Vincent van Gogh complete in his lifetime?",
    "answer": 2100
  },
    {
    "question": "How many Olympic gold medals did Michael Phelps win?",
    "answer": 23
  },
    {
    "question": "How many verses are there in the UK national anthem?",
    "answer": 5
  },
    {
    "question": "How many dimples are there on a standard golf ball?",
    "answer": 336
  },
    {
    "question": "How many films has Tom Hanks appeared in (as of 2025)?",
    "answer": 94
  },
    {
    "question": "How many stairs are there in the Empire State Building?",
    "answer": 1860
  },
    {
    "question": "How many islands make up the Philippines?",
    "answer": 7641
  },
    {
    "question": "How many people were on board the Titanic when it set sail?",
    "answer": 2224
  },
  {
    "question": "How many miles long is the Great Wall of China?",
    "answer": 13000
  }
]